Wolff, Sidney A. Additional Arbitration Files 5637
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Frito-Lay - Jova (Box 4)
  - Guild of New York Nursing Homes versus Clarence Morgan Local #144 - Management Rights, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Gulf Refining and Marketing Company and the Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union Local 8472 - layoff, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    award and opinion, Agreement (1975), general correspondence, Union's summary Brief, Company brief, supporting documentation, manuscript notes
  - Gulf Oil Corporation and Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union Local 8-651 - violation seniority', 1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - H.C.S. Trucking Service and the Teamsters Local 804 - (1 issue), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    performance of bargaining unit work done by people outside the bargaining unit petition in the Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of Queens involving HCS Trucking Service and Donald Carey, President and John Doe, secretary Treasurer of Local 804, Delivery and Warehouse Employees of the Teamsters - award and opinion, Notice of Removal - Supreme Court of the State of New York, County of Queens, general correspondence, supporting documentation, manuscript notes
  - Handy and Harman versus United Steelworkers of America -, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York and the Office Employees International Union, Local 153 - vacation schedule, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    includes award and opinion, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - Hercules Incorporated and the International Chemical Workers Union Local 271 - relocation of plastic laboratory facilities, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    award and opinion, general correspondence, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, transcript
  - Hercules Incorporated and the United Paperworkers International Union Local 884 - discontinuation of contributions to the Group Hospitalization and Surgical Insurance Plan, In-Hospital Medical Plan and the Major medical plan for its furloughed employees, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, brief on behalf of the union "furloughed" assumed from context; "furloughed" is what is actually written, which is not at all a word.
  - High Standard Manufacturing Company and IAM Local 2037 - discharge, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    award and opinion, general correspondence, transcript, Employer Brief, supporting documentation, manuscript notes "Employer" might also be "Employee" or "Employees" as it was written "Employer" originally; verify
  - Hoerner Waldorf Corporation and the United Paperworkers International Union Local 425 - improperly denied employment, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, transcripts, company brief, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, general correspondence
  - Holmdel Township Board of Education - Holmdel Township Education Association, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Honeywell Farms and Teamsters Local 584 - discharge, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - Hooker Chemicals and Plastics Corporation and the Niagara Hooker Employees Union - sub-contracting, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    arbitration report and fee statement, general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, union brief
  - Hooker Chemical Corporation and the IAM Local 2112 - sub-contracting, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, arbitration report and fee statement, supporting documentation, general correspondence
  - Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey and Office and the Professional Employees International Union Local 32 - sick leave pay, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, arbitration report and fee statement
  - ICD Rehabilitation and Research Center versus International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 815 -, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union Educational Institute of New Jersey operating the Union Health Center and the Office Employees International Union Local 32 - discharge, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    general correspondence, award manuscript notes, supporting documentation, transcripts (recording of an investigation)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union Educational Institute of New Jersey operating the Union Health Center and the Office Employees International Union Local 32 - discharge, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers Union Educational Institute of New Jersey operating the Union Health Center and the Office Employees International Union Local 32 - discharge, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Jamaica Water Supply Company and the Utility Workers of America Local 374 - wage rates, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Jamaica Water Supply Company and the Utility Workers of America Local 374 - wage rates, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Jewish Hospital and Medical center of Brooklyn and the Association of Salaried Professional Medical Staff - wage increases, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, Agreement (1976)
  - Jova Manufacturing Company and the Teamsters Local 445 - discontinuance of the Employees Retirement Plan, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, company brief, supporting documentation
- Kentile - New England Telephone (Box 5)
  - Kaplan, Isidore versus RWDSU District 65 - Reinstatement, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Kentile Floors, Incorporated and United Rubber Workers Local 457 - alleged misapplication of the contract relative to the resin dispatcher and his helper, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    includes general correspondence, manuscript notes
  - Knicker Bocker Liquors Corporation versus Liquor Salesmen, Local 2, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kollsman Instrument Corporation and OPEIU (Office and Professional Workers International Union) Local 153 - medical benefits, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kollsman Instrument Corporation and IAM District 15 - work done out of classification, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    manuscript note, general correspondence, award and opinion, company brief, union memo, supporting documentation
  - Kollsman Instrument Company and IAM District 15 - severance pay, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    general correspondence, supporting documentation, opinion and award
  - Korvettes, Division of Arlen Realty and Development Corporation and the Retail Clerks International Association Local 888 - discharge; award and opinion, manuscript notes, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    opinion and award, company brief, general correspondence, manuscript notes, supporting documentation; award and opinion, manuscript notes May be two folders
  - Lever Brothers Company and the International Chemical Workers Union Local 51 - work assignment and seniority, layoffs, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, Agreement (1975), Local Agreement (1973), company brief, supporting documentation
  - Lily-Tulip, Division of Owens-Illinois and the Printing Specialties and Paper Products Union Local 470 - suspension (Box 5, Folder 9)
    award and opinion, supporting documentation
  - Lily-Tulip Cup Corporation and the IAM district 47 - sick pay, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Lionel Moran, Incorporated versus United Industrial Workers of North America, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Lockheed Aircraft Service Company and the IAM Lodge 1834 - promotion, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, general correspondence, supporting documentation, company brief
  - Lockheed-Georgia Company versus IAM Lodge 709, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Long Island Water Corporation and the Utility Workers Union of America Local 365 - layoff, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, agreement (1974), transcripts
  - Macy, RH and RWDSW Local1-5 - disciplinary warnings, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, manuscript notes, award and opinion
  - Macy's New York and the RWDSU local 1-5 - discharge, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, general correspondence, supporting documentation
  - Macy, RH and Company and RWDSU Local 1-5 - discharge, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - Macy, RH and Company versus RWDSU local 105, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Macy, RH and RWDSU - suspension, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Master made Furniture Corporation and the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 2632 - holiday pay, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - McCall Printing Company and Dayton Typographical Union Local 57 - work removal that resulted in massive layoff, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    general correspondence, supporting documentation, manuscript notes, employer's reply brief, post hearing brief on behalf of the employer, union brief, union reply brief
  - Metropolitan Jewish Geriatric Center Local 144 Hospital, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Midland Glass Company and Glass Bottle Blowers Association - back pay, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    award and opinion, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, general correspondence, supporting documentation
  - Minnesota Mining and Manufacturing Company and the IAM District 47 - suspension, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Mobil Oil Corporation and the Industrial Petroleum Workers - discharge, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    transcripts, manuscript notes, arbitration report and fee, award and opinion, union brief, company brief, general correspondence
  - Mobilization for Youth and the Community and Social Agency Employees Union Local 1707 - job status, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Morse Chain Company and the IAM Local Lodge 520 - arbitrability and violation of seniority rights, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    general correspondence, award and opinion, supporting documentation
  - National Broadcasting Company Incorporated versus Alan Douglas, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - National broadcasting Company, Incorporated and NABET Local 11 - alleged improper transfer, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    general correspondence, notice of hearing
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC) versus NABET, Local 11, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC) versus IATSE, Local 771, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - National Broadcasting Company (NBC) and the IATSE Local 771 - restoration to job classification (downgrading), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    award and opinion, general correspondence, manuscript notes, Agreement (1974), post hearing memorandum, company brief, supporting documentation
  - National Hose and Tubing Company versus United Rubber Workers, Local 162, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Natron Corporation versus United Papermakers and Paperworkers, Local 307, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Newark Steel Drum Company, Incorporated and the Teamsters Local 1034 - transfer, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    manuscript notes, general correspondence, award and opinion
  - New England Telephone Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2222, 2313, 2315, 2320-27 - plant sales program, discipline and discharge, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Award and opinion, general correspondence, manuscript notes, clippings
- New England Tile - Publishers (Box 6)
  - New England Telephone Company versus International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2222, 2313, 2315, 2320-27 - discipline and discharge, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    manuscript notes, general correspondence, Statement of Facts and Issues, opinion and award
  - New England Telephone Company versus the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2222, 2313, 2315, 2320-27 - suspension and discharge, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    award and opinion, arbitration bill, manuscript notes
  - New England Telephone and Telegraph Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 2222, 2313, 2315, 2320-27 - suspension and discharge, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, general correspondence, union brief, civil action suit - decree for declaratory judgment
  - New Era Lettering Company versus District 65, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company and the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 827 - discharges, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Bell Company and IBEW - pay treatment, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, Agreement (1968)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company versus IBEW Local 827, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. IBEW Local 827, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - New York City Office of Labor Relations versus AFSCME District Council 37 - arbitrability, creation of new job, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, correspondence
  - New York City Police Department versus Captain's Endowmen Association, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    notes only
  - New York Hotel Supply versus Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America - vacation pay, lay-off, transfers, sub-contracting, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    general correspondence, 1963 Agreement, manuscript notes
  - New York News versus Newspaper Guild of New York, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - New York Telephone Company and the Communication Workers of America Local 1122 - suspension, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, photographs, maps, Court Record - (State of New York, County of Erie - Notice of Motion, Western States District Court, Western District of New York - Order)
  - New York Telephone Company and the Communication Workers of America Local 1122 - suspension, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, transcripts
  - New York Telephone Company and the Communication Workers of America Local 1106 - promotional bypass, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    opinion and award, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, general correspondence, supporting documentation
  - New York Telephone Company versus Telephone Employees Organization - Accounting, Downstate, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - New York Telephone Company versus CWA, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Newburgh City and the Newburgh Police Benevolent Association - whether PBA President entitled to be relieved of scheduled duty to attend monthly conference in Albany, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    opinion and award, manuscript notes, hearing (City of Newburgh - New York) supporting documentation
  - The Northeastern Program Service Center and the American Federation of Government Employees Local 1760 - Promotion Grievance, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    award and opinion, Petition for reconsideration and reopening of Petition for review of arbitration award and stay of execution of award - before the United States Federal Labor Relations Council (1978), Petition for review of decision and award of Arbitrator Sidney A Wolf and request for stay of execution of award (1977) - before the US Federal Labor Relations Council Company is petitioner; general correspondence, statement of facts and issues, supporting documentation, union brief, transcript
  - Northeastern Program Service Center and the American Federation of Government Employees (Local?) - Discipline, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    arbitration bill, hearing before the federal mediation and conciliation service (opinion and award), general correspondence, company brief, supporting documentation, transcript, manuscript notes Local indecipherable
  - Nuway Distributing Corporation versus Amalgamated Union Local 355, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - One Stop Community Day Care Center and the American Federation of County State and Municipal Employees DC 1707 - discharge, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Arbitration bill, award and opinion, union brief, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, general correspondence
  - Otis Elevator Company and the International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Local 453, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    opinion and award, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, arbitration bill, discharge case
  - Otis Elevator Company and the International Union of Electrical Workers Local 484 - seniority and promotion, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Otis Elevator Company and the International Union of Electrical Workers Local 484 - disciplinary suspension, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    manuscript notes, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - Otis Elevator Company and the International Union of Electrical Workers (Box 6, Folder 27)
    miscellaneous correspondence and issues
  - Petroleum Heat and Power Company, Incorporated and the Petroleum Heat and Power Workers Association - holiday pay, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Pinkerton's Incorporated versus Service Employees International Union Local 238, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Pippin Company versus American Federation of Musicians Local 802, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    award and opinion, general correspondence
  - Planetary Recreations, Reputable Concessions versus Allied Service Employees Union, Local 144 - dues, initiation fees, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    manuscript notes, award, general correspondence
  - Plastic Coating Corporation versus IAM Lodge 1544 - rates of pay, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    award, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - Playboy Club versus Dining Room Employees Local I, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - PPG Industries versus Allied Chemical and Alkali Workers, Local I, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Princess Ribbon Corporation and Empress Novelty Company and the Fur Service Division, FLM Joint Board, A.M.C. and B.W. of NA - wage increases, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    award, manuscript notes, extension Agreement (1970)
  - Proctor and Gamble Manufacturing Company and the Independent Oil and Chemical Workers, Incorporated - discharge, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, award, arbitration bill, transcript, company brief, union brief
  - Procter and Gamble Manufacturing Company and the Independent Oil and Chemical Workers, Incorporated - wage rates, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    general correspondence, transcript, company brief, reply brief for the company, union brief, reply brief on behalf of the union, supporting documentation, manuscript notes
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union Local 153 and the International Ladies Garment Workers Union Local 105 - holiday pay dispute, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    award, general correspondence, supporting documentation (Placement of folder? Claims in the original list to be alphabetical based on Professional.)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas Company versus Gas Workers Local 274, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Public Service Electric and Gas Company and the Public Utility Construction and Gas Appliance Workers Union of New Jersey Local 274 - Job Description: Work Assignment, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Award, general statement, correspondence, transcript, Agreement (1971), arbitration report and fee statement, manuscript notes, general correspondence
  - Publishers' Association of New York City and the New York Typographical Union Number 6 - (3 related issues), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Issue: Should the New York Times be required to pay interest on the amount owed by it for its use of outside tape under the provisions of the 1963 and 1965 agreements between the parties from the time agreement on the formula for determining the amount of such payment was actually made? The rate of interest and if the NY Times makes monthly installments the rate of interest on such monthly payments Includes: general correspondence, issues and award, manuscript notes, Publishers' Memorandum, Union Memorandum, clippings, Escrow Agreement (1966)
- Quad - Sheiners (Box 7)
  - New York Typographical Union Number 6 and the Quad Typographers, Incorporated - discharge, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - RCA Corporation and the Radio Communications Assemblers Union - downgrading, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    transcripts, employer brief, award and opinion, manuscript notes, supporting documentation
  - RCA Service Company and the IBEW Local 1452 - discharge, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    arbitration bill, manuscript notes, award and opinion, transcript (2 volumes), company brief, Agreement (1969), general correspondence, supporting documentation
  - Robertshaw Controls and UAW Local 376 - layoff/seniority bumping, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    manuscript notes, transcripts, award and opinion
  - Robertshaw Controls and UAW Local 376 - holiday pay, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    award and opinion, arbitration bill, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, transcripts, company post hearing brief
  - Roosevelt Hospital and Teamsters - sub-contracting, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    award and opinion, general correspondence, manuscript notes, company brief, memo from the union, supporting documentation
  - Rowe Industries versus IBEW Local 485, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Royal Crest Convalescent Home: District 1199, National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees and the Geriatric Care Nursing Center of Waterbury, Incorporated - work schedule, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    opinion and award, general correspondence, manuscript notes
  - Royal McBee Corporation and the UAW local 937 - layoff/seniority, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    supporting documentation, manuscript notes, arbitration bill, award and opinion, transcript, comments on the union brief, union comments on company brief, supporting documentation
  - San A. and Company, Incorporated versus Amalgamated Local 355, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Scheiner's West (?) versus Retail Dry Goods Local 1102 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schenuit Industries versus United Rubber Workers Local 293, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Schulton, Incorporated, a division of American Cyanamid and the Teamsters Local 892 - sub-contracting and the transferring of work, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    arbitration bill, transcripts (3 volumes), manuscripts notes, supporting documentation, Summation, opinion and award, statement of facts and memorandum of law on behalf of the teamsters
  - Scott Paper Company and the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers - job posting, seniority in promotion, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    arbitration bill, general correspondence, supporting documentation, award and opinion, manuscript notes, company brief, union brief
  - Sealright Company versus UPIU Local 547, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Sealtest Foods Incorporated and the Teamsters - discharge, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    general correspondence, award, manuscript notes
  - Simmonds Precision and the International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers Local 452 - suspension, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    general correspondence, manuscript notes, supporting documentation, arbitration bill, award and opinion
  - South Central Bell and CWA - suspension, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    arbitration bill, award and opinion, manuscript notes, transcripts, Agreement (1974), supporting documentation, general correspondence
  - South Central Bell Telephone Company versus Communication Workers of America (no local) - suspension, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    correspondence, transcript, notes, etc.
- Social Security - Union Carbide (Box 8)
  - Social Security Administration, Department of Health Education and Welfare and the New York-New Jersey Council of District Office Locals of the American Federal Government Employees (1 issue), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)